fix: resolve AboutSettings save issues and complete recent features

- Fix double-wrapping of block arrays in ManageAboutPage mutateFormDataBeforeSave
- Add missing type wrappers to builder blocks in mutateFormDataBeforeFill to fix data dropping on load
- Add migration to include contact_email, contact_phone, and address to AboutSettings
- Update auth views, layout components, and company footer
- Implement NewsletterSubscribe Livewire component and tests
- Add FormationSection component and corresponding tests
- Clear and rebuild caches for spatie/laravel-settings
